Jeff Bezos at
Amazon, and I
think this
was in 1999.
with some glee,
announced on
Amazon's earnings call
that Amazon was
going to lose
so much more
money in the
next year because
Amazon, Jeff, had
decided this opportunity
was so much
bigger than anyone
understood.
And by the
way, he was
right. It was
going to take
much longer.
That he
had to up
the capital
spending budget.
And what happened
that day?
The stock
just soared.
And
one of our
panelists on
our brainstorm this
week reminded me
that a
journalist asked
Jeff, "Well, how
do you spell
profit in this
new world?
What does
that mean?"
And he spelled
it P-R-O-P-H-E-T.
So that's
how cavalier
CEOs of
innovation-based companies
were back then,
those driving the
innovation.
And then, of
course, they paid
a heavy price
for that